John Gay Collection 1916-2002 LCP2002/001
Liberian Collections
- Publications
  - Miscellaneous
    - Liberian Studies Association Conference Program & Letters to Participants, Allen R. Boyd, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Addresses Given at the University of Libera, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, undated (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, undated (Box 10)
    - Oral Literature William P. Murphy, undated (Box 10)
    - University of Liberia Special Convocation Program, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Newsletters & Magazines
    - Africa Confidential, 1991 (Box 10)
    - BMC News, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Contact,, undated, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Cuttington Review, 1961 - 1972 (Box 10)
    - Cuttington Review, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Focus on Liberia, 1993 - 2000 (Box 10)
    - Friends of Liberia, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Interculture News, 1973 (Box 10)
    - LAMCO News, 1971 (Box 10)
    - LibUNESCO, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Liberia, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Liberia Alert, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Liberia Official Gazette, 1970 - 1971 (Box 10)
    - Liberia Watch, 1990 - 1991 (Box 10)
    - Liberian Education Review, 1962 - 1963 (Box 10)
    - Liberian Research Association, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Lofaland, 1992 - 2000 (Box 10)
    - Lutheran, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Pepperbird, 1993 - 1997 (Box 10)
    - Revelation, 1973 (Box 10)
    - SUB, 1972 - 1973 (Box 10)
    - Teachers College Bulletin, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Topic, undated (Box 10)
    - Torch,, undated, 1971 - 1972 (Box 10)
  - Official Reports
    - Agency for International Development, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Annual Agency Report Peter G. Dorliae, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Department of Education, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Department of Education, G. Flamma Sherman, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Department of Public Information, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Education and World Affairs, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Ethnographic Survey of Southeastern Liberia, Prelimnary Report on the KRU, Kjell Zetterstrom, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Family Planning Association of Liberia, William A. Hill, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Friends of Liberia, 1994 - 1996 (Box 10)
    - Hunger and Starvation in Africa, Reverand Thomas E. Hayden & Richard J. Massaro, 1985 (Box 10)
    - International Labour Office, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Ministry of Education, G. Flamma Sherman, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Notes on Literacy Training at Camp Schiefflin Richard L. Bethards, 1965 - 1967 (Box 10)
    - OPEX Quarterly Report, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Phebe Health Center, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Report on Liberia Human Rights Issues, Reverand Thomas Hayden, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Republic of Liberia Ministry of Agriculture, C.E. Van Santeri, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Society for the Conservation of Nature of Liberia, undated (Box 10)
    - Western Council of the Association for Teacher Education in Africa, Mary Antoinette Brown Sherman, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Zorzor Teacher Training Institute, Liberia, 1975 (Box 10)
  - People & Culture of Liberia
    - Artist Archetype in Gola Culture, Warren D'Azevedo, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Changing Africa Through Its Eyes, Melissa Pfeiffer, undated (Box 10)
    - Common Principles of Variant Kinship Structures Among the Gola of Western Liberia, Warren D'Azevedo, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Emigrants to Liberia 1820 - 1943, Tom Swick, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Hinterland of Liberia, Sir Alfred Sharpe, undated (Box 11)
    - Immigrants to Liberia 1865 - 1904, Peter Murzda, Jr., 1975 (Box 11)
    - Informational Department of State Publication, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Liberian National Programme of Integrated Rural/Regional Development, C. Campaigne, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Near Edge of Change, Tana Christianssen & John Gay, undated (Box 11)
    - Observing the 1997 Special Elections Processing in Liberia, undated (Box 11)
    - Orientation Towards the Future by Liberian School Children, Ruth Fricke, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Report of the Seminar on Anthropology in Liberia, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Setting of Gola Society and Culture, Warren D'Azevedo, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Tour in the Liberian Hinterland, Braithwaite Wallis, undated (Box 11)
  - Photocopies & Newspaper Clippings
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, undated, 1969 - 1998 (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous Photocopies of Newspaper & Magazine Clippings, undated, 1976 - 1998 (Box 11)
  - Scholarly Works
    - Articles by William Murphy, 1980 - 1981 (Box 11)
    - Black American Images of Liberia 1977 - 1974, Lenwood Davis, undated (Box 11)
    - Doctoral Thesis David Lancy, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Doctoral Thesis Leon Weintraub, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Kpelle: A Study of Political Change in the Interior of Liberia, Fulton, undated (Box 11)
    - Kpelle of Liberia, James Gibbs, undated (Box 11)
    - Liberian Educational and Cultural Research Project, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Management Practices and Prospects: A Study of the Liberian Agricultural Sector, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Mediation and Transfer in Concept Formation, Joseph Glick, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Occupational Expectations and Status Attainments Among Librarians, Konia Kolleloh, undated (Box 11)
    - Papers from the Seminar of Liberian Educators for the Liberia Training Project, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Profile of Liberian Women in Development, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Profile of Liberian Women in Marketing, Brahima Kaba, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Reasons Why Mano Students Drop Out of School, Lawrence Taryor & John Gay, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Report on Teacher Manpower Study in Liberia, Igolima Amachree & Jabaru Carlon, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Research on the History of the Liberian Press, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Standardization of Liberian Ethnic Nomenclature, Svend Holsoe, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Student Case Study Simeon Cole, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Julius Alade, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Julius Alade, Okon Ekanem, William Eastlake, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Emmanuel Ayodele, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Olutokunbo Disu, John Gay, Carter Zerbe, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay JSM Massaquoi & John Gay, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Neo Mnumzana, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay John O'Grady, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Gabriel Olaniawo, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Mellissa Pfeiffer & John Gay, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Student Essay Robert Steward, John Gay, Carter Zerbe, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Student Thesis Roberto Dole & John Gay, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Student Thesis Gordon Thomasson, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Student Thesis Webster Urey & John Gay, 1973 (Box 12)